(Sheldon:)That would be my understanding.
(Sheldon:)On a less painful subject,
(Sheldon:)what size T-shirt do you take?
(Sheldon:)Raj, you were being
a good friend,
(Sheldon:)and my illness was no
excuse for my behavior.
(Sheldon:)I hope that you can
accept my apology.
(Raj:)Of course I do.
(Sheldon:)And, Emily, I'm sorry
for saying dermatologists
(Sheldon:)aren't real doctors.
(Sheldon:)And I'm sure you're
tired of hearing that.
(Emily:)Do you honestly think
I hear that a lot?
(Sheldon:)Well, I would imagine
when your job is popping zits
(Sheldon:)and squirting Botox
into old lady faces...
Okay!
(Raj:)Okay, the point is
(Raj:)that we accept
your apology.
(Emily:)Uh, maybe you do.
(Emily:)He just insulted me again.
(Raj:)Yeah, but he
doesn't mean it.
(Emily:)Why are you defending him?
(stammers) I believe
I can answer that.
(Sheldon:)Uh, like me,
(Sheldon:)Raj is demonstrating empathy.